{
    "subject": "resource/Phillip_Goodhand-Tait",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/East_Riding_of_Yorkshire",
    "human_readable": "Phillip Goodhand-Tait was born in East Riding of Yorkshire.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9585315585136414,
            "question": "Did Phillip Goodhand-Tait live in East Riding of Yorkshire his whole life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9262393712997437,
            "question": "Where was Phillip Goodhand-Tait born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8470346927642822,
            "question": "What is significant about the location where Phillip Goodhand-Tait was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7970198392868042,
            "question": "What year was Phillip Goodhand-Tait born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7939278483390808,
            "question": "In what region of England was Phillip Goodhand-Tait born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6592408418655396,
            "question": "Are there any notable people from East Riding of Yorkshire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6433351039886475,
            "question": "What is Phillip Goodhand-Tait known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5699308514595032,
            "question": "Can you find any historical records related to Phillip Goodhand-Tait's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5256329774856567,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Phillip Goodhand-Tait's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3942461907863617,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Phillip Goodhand-Tait's early life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Phillip Goodhand-Tait was born in East Riding of Yorkshire.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4206_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Phillip Goodhand-Tait's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4206_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you find any historical records related to Phillip Goodhand-Tait's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4206_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Phillip Goodhand-Tait known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4206_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4206_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4206_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4206_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4206_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4206_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4206_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4206_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4206_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4206_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4206_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Phillip Goodhand-Tait was born in Hull, East Riding of Yorkshire, England (multiple times), which supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that Phillip Goodhand-Tait was born in Hull, East Riding of Yorkshire, England."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}